aha-now.com 2017-01-27

# Privacy Policy | Aha!NOW

At Aha!NOW, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We will not release any member information  
unless under court or government order to do so.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://www.aha-now.com, and how we safeguard your information.

 **Personal Information Collection and Cookies**

We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We do not share personal information with third parties nor do we store information we collect about your visit to this blog for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings.

We are not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this blog on other Web sites or media done without our permission. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

 **Advertisers and DoubleClick DART**

We also use third party advertisements on Aha!NOW to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

 **Opt-Out**

You can opt-out of DoubleClick ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

As regards to the forum and membership at Aha!NOW, we do not monitor private messages. But we will investigate all allegations of PM abuse. We further, reserve our right to disable any account at any time for any reason and without notice.

If there are any rules or policies you do not understand, please contact us via email (admin@aha-now.com) or contact form at http://www.aha-now.com.

We reserve the right to modify and amend these terms at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to remain informed of current Aha!NOW privacy policies.

updated: 9th July 2014
